Contact

abhinavkmr86@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/abhinav-kumar-2600a7115 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office Microsoft Excel Microsoft Word

Languages

English (Elementary)

Honors-Awards SCHOLARSHIP

Abhinav Kumar

Undergraduate in Mechanical Engineering Raipur

Summary

Experienced Chairperson with a demonstrated history of working in the automotive industry. Skilled in Suspension, English, Java, and Microsoft Word. Strong administrative professional with a BTech - Bachelor of Technology focused in Mechanical Engineering from National Institute of Technology Raipur.

Experience

NIT Raipur MotoSports RECEPTION CHAIR July 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months) Raipur Area, India

Deisel locomotive workshop Internship Trainee June 2018 - July 2018 (2 months) Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh, India

Education

National Institute of Technology Raipur

BTech - Bachelor of Technology, Mechanical Engineering (2016 - 2020)